- 이해가 안 가네
- 뭐가?
-Oh, I don't know.
-What?
나이가 몇인데
Well, as old as he is
in dog years...
스누피가 지금까지 이런 걸
탈 수 있는 거야?
...do you think Snoopy should
still be flying this thing?
- 레이첼
- 네?
Rachel?
Yeah?
Remember when you first came here and
you got trained by another waitress?
레이첼 처음 왔을 때 다른
웨이트리스한테 교육 받았었죠?
Sure! Do you need me
to train somebody new?
그럼요
제가 신참 교육시킬까요?
재밌네요
Good one.
테리가 레이첼을 다시
교육시키고 싶대요
Actually, Terry wants you
to take the training again.
Whenever.
아무 때나요
Do you believe that?
말이 되니?
Yeah.
으응...
The One Where Rachel Quits
마카롱 두 상자예요
So that's two boxes
of the Holiday Macaroons.
휘파람새 회원 일동을
대표하여 경례 올립니다
On behalf of the Brown Birds of America,
I salute you.
인정해, 챈들러
넌 백핸드가 영 아니올시다야
Just admit it. You have no backhand.
웃기지 마
난 백핸드의 명수라구
Excuse me, little one.
I have a very solid backhand.
얼굴 가리고 여자애처럼 소리
지르는 게 무슨 백핸드의 명수야?
Shielding your face
and shrieking like a girl...
...is not a backhand.
소리는...
해병대처럼 지른 거야
I was shrieking...
...Iike a Marine.
좋아, 챔피언 되는 데 필요한
세 가지를 댈 테니까 잘 들어
All right, watch me execute
the three P's of championship play.
힘!
Power...
정확도!
... precision...
그리고 허풍
...and panache.
꼬마애 다리를 부러뜨렸어?
You broke a little girl's leg?
I know. I feel horrible, okay?
알아, 나도 미치겠어
어제 '세서미 스트리트'에서
인형 하나가 테러 당했다는데
It says here that a Muppet got whacked
on Sesame Street last night.
너 10시경에 어디 있었어?
Where exactly were you around 10-ish?
I'm going to see her.
I wanna bring her something.
지금 보러 갈거야
뭐라도 사 가고 싶은데
뭘 좋아할까?
-What would she like?
-A Hello Kitty doll?
헬로 키티 인형?
아님 걸을 수 있는 능력?
The ability to walk?
난 재교육 받으러 가야지
I'm gonna get back to retraining.
All right. See you, guys.
좋아, 나중에 보자
조심해, 얘들아
범인 납신다
Look out, kids! He's coming!
난 크리스마스 트리
팔러 가야지
I gotta go sell Christmas trees.
잘 해라
잠깐, 그럼 안돼
Have fun.
Oh, wait! No, don't!
깜빡했는데
너 그러면 절대 안돼
I forgot. I am totally
against that now.
일하면 안된다고?
What? Me having a job?
No, I am against innocent trees
being cut down in their prime...
아니, 잘 자라고 있는
죄없는 나무를 잘라 그 시체에...
...and their corpses
grotesquely dressed...
전등이랑 구슬이랑
괴상하게 매다는 거 말야
...in, like, tinsel and twinkly lights.
그러고 잠이 오니?
How do you sleep at night?
나무 끌고 다니느라고
피곤해서 곯아 떨어져
Well, I'm pretty tired
from lugging the trees around.
피비,
네가 잘못 생각하는 거야
You got this all wrong. Those trees
were born to be Christmas trees.
그 나무들은 크리스마스 트리로
태어났어, 임무에 충실해야지
They're fulfilling their life purpose
by making people happy.
사람들을 기쁘게 해야 하잖아
Really?
정말?
그래
Yes!
Yes, and the trees are happy too...
나무들도 기뻐할 거야, 뉴욕을
볼 수 있는 유일한 기회거든
...because for most of them,
it's their only...
...chance to see New York.
음료수를 나른 후에
빈 쟁반은...
After you deliver the drinks,
take the tray
여기서 일한 지 2년이 넘었어요
빈 쟁반 여기 두는 거 알아요
Gunther, please. I have worked here
for two and a half years.
I know the empty trays go over there.
여기 두면 어떨까요?
What if you put them here?
그것도 좋은 생각이네요
컵 있는 데랑 가까우니까요
That's actually a good idea.
They'll be closer to the mugs.
다른 웨이트리스한테도
그렇게 시키는 게 좋겠어요
You should have the other
waitresses do that too.
다들 그렇게 하고 있어요
그래서 여기가 '쟁반 두는 곳'이죠
They already do.
That's why they call it the tray spot.
I heard them talk about that. I just
thought it was a club they went to.
맙소사, 다른 사람들 하는 얘길
들었는데 클럽 얘긴 줄 알았어요
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
미안해요
괜찮아요
자기...
Sweetheart.
그렇게 나쁘진 않지?
So this must be kind of neat
for you, huh?
학교 며칠 쉬기로 했으니까
쿠키 안 팔아도 되잖아
Your dad tells me
you get school off...
...and you don't have to sell
those cookies anymore.
I kind of wanted to sell the cookies.
전 쿠키 팔고 싶어요
Whoever sells the most
wins a trip to Space Camp...
제일 많이 파는 학생이 우주
캠프에서 우주선도 탈 수 있어요
...and gets to sit in a real shuttle.
You really like
all this space stuff, huh?
우주 여행을 좋아하나 보구나?
My dad says if I'd spend as much
time helping him clean apartments...
아빠가 우주 여행 꿈 꿀 시간에
아파트 청소나 도와주면
...as I do daydreaming
about outer space...
... he'd be able to afford a trip
to the Taj Mahal.
타지 마할에도 보내줄 수
있다고 하셨어요
인도까지 가려면 아파트
전체 청소를 도와줘야 할걸
You'd have to clean a lot of apartments
to go all the way to lndia.
아틀란틱 시티에 있는 것만요
아빠는 슬롯 머신을 좋아하세요
No. The one in Atlantic City.
Dad loves the slots.
할머니가 제 앞으로 남겨주신
대학 등록금을 불려주신대요
He says he'll double the college
money Grandma left me.
Well, good luck to Dad.
행운을 빈다고 전해라
이기려면 몇 상자를 더
팔아야 하니?
Say, how many more boxes would you
have to sell in order to win?
작년에 우승한 학생이
475상자를 팔았어요
The girl who won last year sold 475.
- 그런데?
- 전 75상자 팔았어요
So far, I've sold 75.
Four hundred, huh?
4백 상자를 팔아야 되는구나?
못할 것도 없지
Well, that sounds doable.
How much are the boxes?
한 상자에 얼마니?
Five dollars a box.
5달러요
2등상은 뭐니?
And what is second prize?
자전거요
A 10-speed bike. But I'd rather have
something my dad couldn't sell.
아빠가 팔 수 없는 걸
받고 싶어요
그거 말 된다
Well, that makes sense.
Could you do me one favor?
부탁 좀 들어주실래요?
괜찮으시면요
그래, 뭐든 말해
Yeah, Sarah. Anything.
커튼 좀 열어주실래요?
Could you pull the curtains open?
우주비행사 얘기가
뉴스에 나올 건데
The shuttle astronauts
are gonna be on the news.
여긴 TV가 없어서 건너편
아줌마가 창으로 보게 해주신대요
We don't have a TV,
so the lady across the alley...
...said she'd push hers up
to her window so I can watch it.
네?
Yes?
Hi. I'm selling
Brown Bird cookies.
안녕하세요
휘파람새 쿠키 팔러 왔어요
휘파람새 꼬마가 아니잖아
구멍으로 다 보여
You're no Brown Bird.
I can see you through my peephole.
Hi. I'm an honorary Brown Bird.
안녕하세요
전 명예 휘파람새 회원이에요
What does that mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
It means that I can sell cookies,
but I'm not invited to sleepovers.
쿠키를 팔러 온 거지, 잠꾸러기
깨우러 온 게 아니라구요
당장 경찰에 신고할 거야
당장 꺼져!
I can dial 911 at the press
of a button, you know.
Now, go away!
그러지 마시구요, 어린 소녀가
우주 캠프에 가고 싶어해요
Please, please.
It's for a poor little girl...
...who wants to go to Space Camp
more than anything in the world.
- 전화 건다
- 안돼요
I'm pressing.
경찰이 오고 있어
A policeman is on his way.
지금 가요, 가면 되잖아요
Okay, okay!
I'm going, I'm going.
I can still see you!
- 아직도 보여
- 알았어요
All right!
안녕
여긴 웬일이야?
-What are you doing here?
-I thought a lot about what you said...
네가 한 말 생각해봤어
내가 잘못 생각한 것 같아
...and I realize maybe
I was a little judgmental.
하지만...
Yeah. Oh, but, oh.
피비, 잘 생각해봐
Now, now, Phoebe, remember...
...they're just fulfilling
their Christmas
- 크리스마스를 기쁘게 하는 게...
- 운명이라고?
-Destiny. Yes.
-Sure.
- 그래
- 알았어
좋아
알았어
That one doesn't look
very fulfilled.
저것도 임무 수행하러
가는 거야?
너무 늙어서
다시 돌려보내는 거야
That's one of the old ones.
He's just taking it to the back.
늙은 건 돌려보낸다고?
너무 잔인하다
You keep the old ones in the back?
That is so ageist.
그래야 어린 나무를 놓지
We're making room for the fresh ones.
늙은 나무는 어떻게 돼?
So what happens to the old guys?
절단기에 들어가지
They go into the chipper.
나무가 기뻐하는 거 맞아?
I have a feeling that's not
as happy as it sounds.
안돼!
이봐요!
좋아하는 크리스마스
캐릭터가 다 있어
These are shaped like
Christmas characters.
산타, 루돌프, 아기 예수
Santa, Rudolph and Baby Jesus.
난 크림 가득 든
예수 한 상자
I'll take a box of the
cream-filled Jesuses.
겨우 한 상자? 가엾은 꼬마를
우주 캠프에 보내줘야 하는데
One box? I'm trying to send
a little girl to Space Camp.
다섯 상자는 사야지
챈들러, 넌 어때?
I'm putting you down for 5 boxes.
What about you?
코코넛 맛 하느님도 있어?
All right. Do you have any
coconut-flavored deities?
No, but there's coconut in the
Hanukkah Menorah-eos.
아니,
코코넛 맛 하누카 촛대는 있어
I'll put you down for 8 boxes.
One for each night.
여덟 상자 갖다줄게
하루에 한 개씩 먹어
Mon?
모니카?
난 민트 맛으로 한 상자
I'll take a box of the Mint Treasures.
한 상자면 돼
One, and that's it.
휘파람새 회원 되면서
몸무게가 불었잖아
I gained weight after
I joined the Brown Birds.
아빠가 한 상자씩 살 때마다
내가 다 먹어치웠거든
Remember? Dad bought every one
of my boxes and I ate them all.
그게 아니지
No, Mon. Dad had to buy
every one of your boxes...
네가 다 먹어치우니까
아빠가 한 상자씩 사신 거지
... because you ate them all.
But, you know, I'm sure that's
not gonna happen this time.
어쨌든 이번엔 그럴 일
없을 거야
민트 맛 세 상자,
루돌프 두 상자 사라
Why don't I put you down for 3 Mint
Treasures and a couple of Rudolphs?
안돼
No.
Oh, come on, now.
You know you want them.
너도 먹고 싶잖아
안돼, 이러지 마
Don't do this.
I'll tell you what,
I'll give you the first box for free.
있잖아, 모니카
한 상자는 공짜로 줄게
안돼, 나 갈래!
Oh, God! I gotta go!
예쁜 아가들은
다 쿠키를 먹어요
Come on! All the cool kids
are eating them.
And later, I'll show you why
we don't just trap spiders...
좀 있다가, 왜 커피잔에 거미를
안 잡는지 가르쳐줄게요
... under coffee mugs
and leave them there.
좋아하지도 않는 일에 재교육을
받다니, 인생이 왜 이러냐
I'm training to be better at a job
that I hate. My life officially sucks!
임시 직장이었잖아
패션 일 하고 싶어하지 않았어?
Wasn't this supposed to be temporary?
You wanted to do fashion stuff.
맞아, 지금도 알아보고 있어
Yeah, I'm still pursuing that.
How, exactly, are you pursuing that?
어떻게 알아보는데?
2년 전에 이력서 보낸 거
말고 또 뭐하고 있는데?
Other than sending out resumes,
like, what? Two years ago?
좋은 생각들 많이 하고 있지
Well, I'm also sending out...
...good thoughts.
지금 이 일을 하고 있는 한
다른 직장 구하긴 힘들 거야
If you ask me, as long as you
got this job...
...you got nothing pushing you
to get another one.
You need The Fear.
너한테는 '두려움'이 필요해
두려움?
-The Fear?
-He's right.
맞아, 여길 관두면 정말 하고
싶은 일을 할 동기가 생기는 거지
Quit this job, and you'll have motivation
to go after a job you really want.
그러는 넌 왜 싫어하는 일을 해?
너도 관두고 두려움을 가져봐
Why are you still at a job you hate?
Why don't you quit and get The Fear?
Because I'm too afraid.
난 너무 무서워서 안돼
I don't know. I'd give anything
to work for a designer or a buyer.
모르겠다, 디자이너나 바이어가
되려면 뭐든 하고 싶은데
서른 살 돼서도 여기서
일하고 싶지는 않아
I just don't want to be 30
and still work here.
스물 여덟에 여기서 일하는
것보다 훨씬 더 끔찍하다
Yeah, that'd be much worse than
being 28 and still working here.
- 레이첼
- 네?
어느 게 디카페인이고
어느 게 레귤러인지 말해볼래요?
Remind me to review with you which
pot is decaf and which is regular.
손잡이를 보면 되잖아요
Can't I just look at the handles
on them?
그럴까요?
You would think.
좋아요, 건터
그거 알아요?
Okay, fine. Gunther, you know what?
I am a terrible waitress.
난 형편없는 웨이트리스예요
왜 그런 줄 알아요?
Do you know why I'm a terrible waitress?
Because I don't care.
관심이 없으니까요
I don't care which pot
is regular and which pot is decaf.
어느 게 레귤러인지
디카페인인지 관심이 없다구요
쟁반 두는 곳이 어딘지
관심없어요, 원하는 일이 아녜요
I don't care where the tray spot is.
I just don't care.
This is not what I want to do.
So I don't think I should do it anymore.
그래서 그만할 거예요
-I'm giving my week's notice.
-What?
- 일주일 시간을 드릴게요
- 네?
나 관둘래요
Gunther, I quit.
그럼 이제부터 커피값
내야 되는 거야?
Does this mean we have to start
paying for coffee?
좋아, 12, 22, 18...
Okay, 12.
Twenty-two.
Eighteen.
What?
왜?
내가 '유방'이라고 썼어
I spelled out "boobies".
오빠, 나 민트 맛 한 상자
더 줘
Put me down for another box
of the Mint Treasures, okay?
Where are the Mint Treasures?
민트 맛 어딨어?
We're out. I sold them all.
떨어졌어, 다 팔렸어
뭐?
What?
모니카, 그만 먹어
Monica, I'm cutting you off.
안돼, 두 상자만 줘
Just a couple more boxes.
많은 것도 아니잖아
난 괜찮아
It's no big deal, all right? I'm cool.
두 상자만 더 달란 말야
You gotta help me
with a couple more boxes!
모니카, 그만해
쿠키가 목까지 찼어
Look at yourself.
You have cookie on your neck.
Oh, God!
맙소사!
- 지금까지 몇 상자 팔았어?
- 어디 보자
-So how many you sold so far?
-Check this out.
-Five hundred and seventeen boxes!
-Oh, my God! How did you do that?
517 상자
어떻게 그렇게 많이 팔았어?
The other night I was leaving
the museum...
어젯밤 박물관을 나오는 순간
난 완전히 새사람이 됐어
...just as Laser Floyd was letting out
of the planetarium.
50상자나 팔아치웠지
Without even trying, I sold 50 boxes!
성공의 열쇠는 그거였어
무조건 먹이는 거!
That's when it occurred to me.
The key to my success: The munchies.
한밤중에 학교 기숙사를
돌면서...
So I started hitting the NYU dorms
around midnight.
상자 째 쿠키를 팔았어
I am selling cookies by the case.
다들 '쿠키맨'을 찾았지
They call me "Cookie Dude"!
Stop what you're doing. I need
envelope stuffers, stamp lickers....
좋아, 봉투에 이력서 넣고
우표 좀 붙여줘
- 이 이력서 누가 만들어줬어?
- 내가, 컴퓨터로
-Who did these resumes for you?
-Me. On my computer.
글자 크기가 엄청 크다
You sure used a large font.
Yeah. Well, "Waitress at
a Coffeehouse"...
커피숍 웨이트리스, 치어리더 주장,
두 개 뿐이라 공간이 남아서...
...and "Cheer Squad Co-Captain"
only took up so much room.
정말 재밌다, 재밌어
너 정말 웃겼어
Hey, that's funny!
You're funny, Chandler!
You're a funny guy!
또 뭐가 웃긴 줄 알아?
You know what else is funny?
Something else I might have said?
내가 무슨 말을 했는데?
나도 몰라
I don't know. Weren't you the guy
that told me to quit my job...
아무 할 일도 없는데 직장
관두라고 한 거 너 아니었어?
...when I had absolutely
nothing else to do?
진정해, 괜찮을 거야
Calm down. It's gonna be okay.
아니, 괜찮지가 않아
내일이 마지막인데 이게 뭐야
No, it's not gonna be okay.
Tomorrow is my last day...
...and I don't have a lead.
건터한테 전화해서
못 그만둔다고 얘기할 거야
You know what?
I'm just gonna call Gunther...
...and tell him I'm not quitting.
두려움에 굴복하겠다는 거야?
You don't want to give in to The Fear.
'두려움' 소리 하지도 마, 너랑
그 두려움인지 뭔지랑 묶어서...
You and your stupid Fear!
I hate your Fear!
I would like to take
you and your Fear
Hey! I got great news!
좋은 소식이 있어
조이, 살고 싶으면 도망가
Run, Joey! Run for your life!
왜 저래?
What? Rach, listen. Have you ever
heard of Fortunata Fashions?
레이첼, '포투나타 패션'이라고
알아?
아니
아버지가 거기서 일하시는데
사람을 구하고 있대
My dad's got a plumbing job there
and he heard there's an opening.
면접보러 가도 되는지
내가 알아봐줄까?
You want him to get you an interview?
세상에, 그래!
정말 고마워, 조이
Oh, my God, yes! I would love that!
That's so sweet, Joey.
별 거 아냐, 그리고
진짜 좋은 소식이 있어
Not a problem.
And now, for the great news.
그게 좋은 소식 아니었어?
That wasn't the great news?
그거야 생각하기 나름이지
Only if you think
it's better than this.
스프레이 눈이야!
Snow-in-a-Can!
일하는 데서 얻었어
모니카, 크리스마스 분위기 낼래?
You want me to decorate the window?
Give it kind of a Christmas looky?
크리스마스 쿠키 먹자고?
Christmas cookie?
Okay, and this one here's
a Douglas fir.
이것도 좋습니다, 돈을 더
쓰시면 향 좋은 걸 구할 수 있죠
Now, it's a little more money,
but you get a nicer smell.
좋군요, 이걸로 하죠
Looks good. I'll take it.
잠깐, 잠깐
그거 가져가시면 안돼요
Wait, wait. No, no!
You don't want that one!
No, no. You can have
this cool brown one.
이 갈색으로 가져가세요
다 죽었는데요
It's almost dead.
그러니까 사셔야죠
That's why you have to buy it,
to fulfill its Christmas destiny.
그래야 크리스마스 운명에
충실할 수 있거든요
안 그럼 절단기에 들어가요
말 좀 해줘, 조이
Otherwise, they'll throw it
into the chipper. Tell him.
크리스마스 운명을 다하지
못하면 절단기에 들어가요
Yeah, the trees that don't fulfill
their Christmas destiny...
...are thrown in the chipper.
좀 더 둘러보겠습니다
I think I'm gonna look around
a little bit more.
피비?
You gotta stop doing this.
I'm working on commission here!
이러지 마
나 커미션 받고 일한단 말야
얘들아, 나 크리스마스 트리
고르러 왔어
I'm here to pick out
my Christmas tree.
더 볼 것도 없어
이거 가져가
Well, look no further!
This one's yours!
작년에 내가 내다버린 거 아냐?
Is this the one
that I threw out last year?
그런 건 신경쓰지 말고!
성한 건 다 갖고 싶어하잖아
Never mind!
Everybody wants a green one!
미안해, 감정적으로 하지
않으려고 했는데...
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to get so emotional.
The holidays are just hard.
크리스마스는 너무 힘들어
너희 엄마가 크리스마스 때
돌아가셔서 그래?
Oh, honey. Is that because
your mom died around Christmas?
그건 생각도 못했네
I wasn't even thinking about that.
안녕, 몇 개나 팔았니?
Hi there.
How many did you sell?
I'm not gonna tell you. You're the
bad man who broke Sarah's leg.
얘기 안 해요, 아저씨가
사라 다리 부러뜨렸잖아요
그건 사고였단다
Hey, now. That was an accident, okay?
아저씨 못난이
You're a big scrud.
누구더러 못난이래?
What's a scrud?
거울 보면 알잖아요
Why don't you look
in the mirror, scrud?
그럴 필요가 있을까?
네 얼굴 보면 되는데
I don't have to.
I can just look at you.
좋아요, 숙녀분들
그리고 남자분
All right, girls...
...and man.
누구부터 볼까요?
Let's see your final tallies.
Debbie.
데비
쿠키 321상자, 아주 좋아요
Three hundred and twenty-one
boxes of cookies. Very nice.
별 거 아니네
Not nice enough.
샬라...
278상자
Charla.
Two hundred and seventy-eight.
안됐지만... 수고했다
Sorry, dear, but still good.
Good for a scrud.
안됐다, 못난아
엘리자베스는...
Yes, Elizabeth.
871상자
Eight hundred and seventy-one.
말도 안돼!
That's crap!
휘파람새 자매님
Sister Brown Bird.
Good going.
계속하세요
다음은 누구죠?
Who's next?
-Hi there.
-Hi.
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕
And batting for Sarah...
사라 대타...
로스 겔러 씨
... Ross Geller.
872상자
Eight hundred and seventy-two.
Although, it looks like you bought
an awful lot of cookies yourself.
본인이 쿠키를 아주 많이
사셨나 봐요
That is because my doctor
says that I have...
주치의가 하는 말이...
제가 심한...
...a very serious...
쿠키...
... nougat...
결핍이라고 해서요
...deficiency.
그래서 어떻게 됐어
휘파람새 형제님?
Tell us what happened, Brown Bird Ross.
I lost. Some little girl loaned
her uniform to her 19-year-old sister...
우승을 놓쳤어
어떤 꼬마가 19살 먹은 언니한테
옷을 빌려줘서 2천 상자 팔았대
...who went down to the U. S. S. Nimitz
and sold over 2000 boxes.
안녕, 면접은 어땠어?
-How'd the interview go?
-Oh, I blew it.
망쳤지 뭐
나라도 안 뽑을 거야
I wouldn't have even hired me.
이리 와, 괜찮아
Come here, sweetie.
Listen...
직장 얻으려면 2천 번 넘게
면접을 봐야 되는 거야
...you're gonna go on, like,
1000 interviews before you get a job.
그 말을 하려던 게 아닌데
That's not how that was supposed
to come out.
This is just the worst Christmas ever.
올해 크리스마스는 악몽이야
레이첼, 그냥 이 커피숍에서
일하는 게 어때?
Maybe you should just
stay here at the coffeehouse.
안돼, 너무 늦었어
테리가 벌써 저 여자를 뽑았어
I can't. It's too late. Terry already
hired that girl over there.
Look at her.
보라구
웨이트리스 경험도 있대
She's even got waitress experience.
어젯밤엔 다른 사람들한테
냅킨 접는 법을 가르쳐줬대
Last night she was...
...teaching everybody
how to make...
... napkins...
백조 접는 법...
...into....
'백조'래
That word was "swans."
술독에 빠진 산타 때문에
크리스마스를 다 망쳐버렸어
Well, seeing that drunk Santa wet
himself really perked up my Christmas.
세상에
Oh, my God!
메리 크리스마스!
Merry Christmas!
You saved them!
You guys!
고마워, 얘들아
너희밖에 없다
Oh, God, you're the best!
'살아있는 '죽은' 크리스마스
트리들의 밤' 같다
Looks like Night of the
Living Dead Christmas Trees.
여보세요, 전데요
Yeah, this is she.
You're kidding! You're kidding!
설마, 농담이시죠?
Oh, thank you! I love you!
감사합니다, 사랑해요
Sure, everybody loves a kidder.
농담만 잘 하면
인기 짱이지
나 취직됐어
I got the job!
That's great.
God bless us, everyone!
신이 우리 모두를
축복하시나봐
간다, 내가 접대하는
마지막 커피야
Here we go. I'm serving
my last cup of coffee.
There you go.
됐어
Enjoy.
마셔
-Should I tell her I ordered tea?
-No.
- 차 시켰다고 말할까?
- 아니
실례하겠어요, 여러분
오늘이 제 마지막 근무일이에요
Excuse me, everyone?
This is my last night working here...
...and I just wanted to say...
이곳에서 좋은 친구들을
사귀었단 말씀을 드리고 싶네요
...that I made some good friends here.
And it's just time to move on.
하지만 이젠 발전해야죠
And no offense to everybody
who still works here...
계속 여기 근무하시는 분들에겐
미안한 얘기지만
... but you have no idea how good
it feels to say...
지금 이 순간 기쁜 마음으로
이 말씀을 드리고 싶네요
...that as of this moment...
... I will never have
to make coffee again.
저 이제 커피 안 타도 돼요
사장님은 진한 커피를
좋아하시니까 두 스푼을 넣어요
Now, Mr. IKaplan Sr.
Iikes his coffee strong.
So you want to use two bags
instead of one.
잘 봐요
이 부분이 특히 어렵거든요
Now, pay attention.
This part's tricky.
필터를 한 번만 쓰는
사람도 있는데...
See, some people use filters
just once....
I'm sorry you didn't get to go
to Space Camp...
우주 캠프에 못 가게 돼서
안됐지만 이걸로 만족해줄래?
...and I'm hoping that maybe somehow
this may help make up for it. Okay?
Presenting...
소개합니다, 사라 터들의
개인 전용 우주 캠프!
...Sarah Tuddle's
Private Very Special Space Camp!
You don't have to do this.
겔러 아저씨
이렇게까지 안 해도 되는데...
간다!
Oh, come on, here we go!
Stand by for mission countdown!
우주선 발사 카운트다운!
Ten.
10, 10...
9, 9...
Nine.
8, 8...
Eight.
Okay, blast off!
발사!
난 에일리언이다!
에일리언이다!
I'm an alien! I'm an alien!
Oh, no! An asteroid!
소행성이다!